(Howard:)She arranged for us to get a rental car.
(Raj:)Great, we can still make it to Comic-Con.
(Leonard:)Are you kidding me? After all we've
been through? I just want to go home.
(Raj:)Don't be like that.
Come on, Howard, talk to him.
(Howard:)I'm with Leonard. I'm done.
(Raj:)Fine, then I guess it's two against two.
How do we decide?
(Sheldon:)Actually, it's three against one.
What? Well, what about the mission?
You said we're a real-life landing party.
(Sheldon:)Well, we're not.
(Sheldon:)We're an imaginary landing party.
(Sheldon:)Who had real-life garbage thrown at us
by real-life strangers who think we're idiots.
(Sheldon:)And to tell you the truth,
I'm starting to feel like one.
(Sheldon:)I want to go home now.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Raj:)Did we at least rent the car
from Enterprise?
Get it? Enterprise? Heh.
(Raj:)Screw you, that's funny.